harpoonbrewery.com 2013-11-25

# Privacy Policy

Harpoon Brewery understands the importance of privacy and security with regard to exchanging information online. As such, we respect your right to privacy. All detailed information is held in confidence, and is never sold, transferred, shared or solicited to other parties.

To be a Friend of Harpoon, we ask our customers for personal information such as name, address, company name, e-mail address and other details. Providing us with this information simply helps us to better serve our customers. From time to time, our site may request information from customers via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the customer therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (activities, preferences, behavior).

Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of Harpoon's products and this site. Customers' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless the third parties are part of a [Friend of Harpoon](http://www.friendofharpoon.com/) survey or contest.

**Personal Information Privacy**

Harpoon Brewery will take all necessary steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to informational databases, encrypting sensitive information and securing our data with appropriate passwords and user permissions. We will not sell, rent, or share our customers' personal information to other companies for any reason.

We will communicate with customers via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the customer has opted-in and agrees to receive those communications. If you believe that you are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, please inform us and we will remove your name from our distribution lists. If a customer's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a customer no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our estore Customer Support at [estore@harpoonbrewery.com](mailto:estore@harpoonbrewery.com) or our Friend of Harpoon Customer Support at [fohinfo@harpoonbrewery.com](mailto:fohinfo@harpoonbrewery.com). Or, contact us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

If you have any questions or comments on this policy, our use of your information, or other privacy issues, please feel free to contact us.

**The Harpoon Brewery**  
306 Northern Ave  
Boston, MA, 02210[  
info@harpoonbrewery.com](mailto:info@harpoonbrewery.com)
